alwaysonvacation.com 2006-12-08

# PRIVACY - AlwaysOnVacation.com - your vacation rental destination

---  
   
|  |   
---  
|  |   
---  
   
| |    
  |   |    
  |  |   | 

**AlwaysOnVacation.com** understands that making purchases online involves a great deal of trust on your part; we take this trust very seriously, and make it our highest priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal information you provide us. 

|    
---|---|---  
  |  |    
  | What Personal Information Does AlwaysOnVacation.com Collect? |    
  |   |    
  | Transaction Information from Owners and Listing Managers |    
  | At AlwaysOnVacation.com, it is necessary for us to obtain transaction information from you in order to complete your purchase. This includes your name, contact information (used for purchase-related communications only), subscription information, and credit card data. This information is stored with each transaction and shared only with credit card authorization companies. We may also use your e-mail address or telephone number to contact you about status of your subscription or problems with your listing.  |    
  |   |    
  | Owner and Listing Manager Newsletter |    
  | Owners and Listing Managers can choose to receive AlwaysOnVacation.com Owner newsletter with tips and expert advice on managing vacation rentals. To opt out of receiving the newsletter, owners can email : [Ownerunsubscribe@alwaysonvacation.com](mailto:Ownerunsubscribe@alwaysonvacation.com.) |    
  |   |    
  | Transaction Information for Travelers |    
  | At AlwaysOnVacation.com, it is necessary for us to obtain transaction information from you in order to complete your purchase. This includes your name, contact information (used for purchase-related communications only), travel selections, and credit card data. This information is stored with each transaction and shared with appropriate vendors (for example, vacation rental managers) and third parties facilitating the transaction (for example, credit card authorization companies). We will provide only the information necessary to ensure your travel arrangements are confirmed and executed with these providers.  |    
  |   |    
  | Member Profile- My Vacations  |    
  | Members can choose to provide AlwaysOnVacation.com with travel preferences and other personal information. This information is primarily used to assist members in making reservations quickly without having to type in the same information repeatedly. If you don't want to store your personal information, you can still research and book vacation rentals direct from owners. Keep in mind, however, that certain AlwaysOnVacation.com features (for example, stored vacation rental favorites, or the specials newsletter for your specific destinations) are only available to our members. We may also use your e-mail address or telephone number to contact you about changes to your purchased travel itinerary. |    
  |   |    
  | Specials Newsletter |    
  | Members and Non-members can choose to receive AlwaysOnVacation.com newsletter with specials on vacation rentals by supplying their email address. Only members can tailor the newsletter to receive specials and promotions for their choice of destinations. To opt out of receiving the newsletter, members can modify their profile and non-members can send an email to [unsubscribe@alwaysonvacation.com](mailto:unsubscribe@alwaysonvacation.com)   
Or visit http://www.alwaysonvacation.com/newsletter/unsubscribe.html |    
  |   |    
  | Surveys, Contests, and Sweepstakes Information  |    
  | Occasionally, AlwaysOnVacation.com may offer our members and site visitors an opportunity to participate in a survey, contest, or sweepstakes. Information collected by AlwaysOnVacation.com when you participate in a survey, contest, or sweepstakes may include your full name, e-mail address, and street address. Subsequently, we may use your e-mail address to send you information about hot deals, contests, sweepstakes, surveys, promotions, or other travel opportunities offered by AlwaysOnVacation.com and its marketing partners. However, you can ALWAYS opt out of receiving AlwaysOnVacation.com communications by modifying your profile. Simply tell us you're not interested and you won't receive these messages from us again.  |    
  |   |    
  | Cookies |    
  | "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. As a member or visitor to AlwaysOnVacation.com you will be assigned a permanent cookie file on your computer's hard drive. You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your Web browser to refuse cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie. By refusing to accept a cookie, however, you will not be able to access many travel services and planning tools offered by AlwaysOnVacation.com. When you reserve or purchase travel, or use selected travel planning tools, AlwaysOnVacation.com requires you to sign in as a member, using your Member ID and password. Once you sign in as an AlwaysOnVacation.com member, we record the Member ID and the name on the member account in the cookie file on your computer. We may also record your password in this cookie file if you checked the box entitled "Save this password for automatic sign-in." Your Member ID, password, and the name on your member account is stored in the cookie file as encrypted data, so no one can view the information it contains by obtaining unauthorized access to your computer. Permanent cookie files remain on your computer's hard drive until you manually delete the file.  |    
  |   |    
  | Sharing Your Information  |    
  |  |  | When you book travel with AlwaysOnVacation.com, the personal information you provide us will be shared with the appropriate third parties necessary to complete your purchases. This includes the vendors you have selected (e.g., cruiselines, airlines, etc.) as well as the third parties facilitating the transactions (e.g., credit card authorization companies). The personal information we provide these third parties will only be that which is necessary to ensure your travel arrangements are successfully confirmed and executed.   
---|---  
| AlwaysOnVacation.com will sometimes share aggregated data with our service providers. This data does not contain any personal information and is used to develop featured programs and content that will be of interest to our members and site visitors.   
| Occasionally, AlwaysOnVacation.com will hire a third party to act on our behalf for projects such as market research surveys and contest entry processing and will provide information to these third parties specifically for use in connection with these projects. The information we provide to such third parties is protected by a confidentiality agreement and is to be used solely for completing the specific project.   
| When required by law (e.g. court order or subpoena), we may disclose certain personal information.   
| In the event that AlwaysOnVacation.com or certain of its assets are acquired, customer information may be part of the transferred assets  
  |    
   
  | Security |    
  | AlwaysOnVacation.com uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt all your personal information, including credit card information. The process of encryption takes the information you enter and converts it into bits of code that are securely transmitted over the Internet. This scrambled data cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. Once our secure server receives your encrypted personal information, it is translated back into its original form and stored in our off-line database. Your credit card information is not transmitted over the Internet again.  |    
  |   |    
  | Contacting AlwaysOnVacation.com  |    
  | If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@alwaysonvacation.com](mailto:privacy@alwaysonvacation.com) |    
  |   |    
  |   |    
  |     |    
   
  |   |    
  |   |    
Vacation Rentals  |  Destination Guides  |  Sitemap  |  Resources  |  Privacy Policy  
| **Our Partners :** [VacationStreet.com](http://www.vacationstreet.com/ "VacationStreet.com") • [A1Floridarentalvacation.com](http://www.a1floridarentalvacation.com/ "A1Floridarentalvacation.com") • [TravelerPages.com](http://www.travelerpages.com/ "TravelerPages.com")  
---  
**AlwaysOnVacation.com** is fast becoming one of the largest and most accessed travel sites on the internet  
specializing in vacation rental homes. With the 'easy to use' search engine of AlwaysOnVacation.com,   
even novices can easily find and book the most suitable vacation home. AlwaysOnVacation.com also   
provides owners with the means to efficiently promote their Vacation Rental properties. 

Copyright © 2005-06 **[Vacation Renter Solutions](http://www.vacationrenter.com/ "Vacation Renter Solutions")** LLC All Rights Reserved.
